[RAM]
Barusu.
How long will you sleep?
It's time to wake up already.
Barusu.
[yelps]
Where are we?
[RAM] The air around
us is still and cool.
We're most likely underground.
[SUBARU]
Ram?
Underground as in--
Beneath the dunes.
If you believe what
Ms. Beatrice was theorizing
before we were separated,
it's likely because of
a distortion in space.
And that's what sent us
all plummeting down here?
Wait, separated?
Hold on, where
is everyone else?
It seems like it's only you
and me here, so what happened?
I'm not sure why
you're asking me.
[rumbling]
[gripping music]
[gasps]
♪ ♪
[RAM] I don't see any sign
of Ms. Emilia or Ms. Beatrice.
You really blew it this time.
I don't need
your sass right now.
We have to go find the others.
No, wait.
Where's Rem?
Barusu.
We need to find
everyone, obviously,
but Rem is
the priority for now.
She's not even able
to move on her own.
We gotta go.
We have to find her, and quick!
[RAM]
Barusu, you need to calm down.
Calm down?
You expect me
to calm down, really?
What, do you not even
care that Rem's in danger?
You know that's not true!
You're right.
Sorry, I mean it.
I was being an idiot.
Honestly, a total jerkwad.
That's nothing new.
Anyway, I can feel the
faint link I share with Rem.
I still don't have
any idea where she is,
but I can tell
she's alive at least.
That's right,
I forgot, you're twins,
so you have synesthesia.
[ANASTASIA] Natsuki, finally
bright eyed and bushy tailed,
are ya?
[SUBARU]
Lady Anastasia and Patrasche.
Sorry I went and borrowed
her without your permission.
I may be a gutsy gal,
but not enough to go
looking around here
all on my lonesome.
I mean, I don't have
a problem with that, but--
I never said anything about
it being just the two of us
alone here.
How did the surroundings look?
Not promising.
I wasn't able to find an exit,
and none of the others
seemed close by.
Looks like just
the three of us
were sent to this
particular area.
Oh, and I couldn't forget
Patrasche, of course.
We're the only
ones here, then?
[RAM]
No point in crying over it.
Now that Barusu
the useless is awake,
let's look for Rem
and Ms. Emilia.
What, just go
out there blindly?
The universe is laughing at us
with this team formation.
In case you haven't noticed,
none of us can fight!
[theme music]
♪ ♪
I think maybe
I can feel a breeze.
Or maybe not.
[RAM] Can't you speak
with spirits, Barusu?
[SUBARU] Asking the lesser
spirits to guide us, huh?
Problem with that is my link
with Beako is so strong,
all of them are too
scared to deal with me.
[RAM] You're more
the living embodiment
of Ms. Beatrice's pity
than a real magician,
so I had no expectations.
[grumbles]
[ANASTASIA]
Natsuki.
Huh?
She's trying to be brave
and hide it from you,
but really, right after
we tumbled into this place
and before you woke up,
Ram was pretty beside herself,
not being able
to see Rem around.
She panicked?
[ANASTASIA]
All that to say,
you're playing a big
part in keeping her
emotionally stable
through this.
You ain't useless
in the slightest.
[SUBARU]
The path splits here.
Well, that's frustrating.
Feels purposeful too.
What do we do?
According to my knowledge,
it's best to listen to
Freud in times like these
and go right always.
Who's that?
Apparently,
behavioral studies
suggest that humans
tend to default
to choosing the left option.
And so,
my strong sense of justice
tells me to check
the right one instead.
You really seem
to trust this Freud a lot.
Again, who the heck is that?
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
Uh-- a door?
It's huge and it
looks thick too.
Can we even move it?
[ANASTASIA] For starters, it
looks completely sealed shut,
so it'd be tough.
But also, Natsuki,
I wondered what makes you
think this is a door anyway?
It just looks like a plain old
iron wall to me, nothing more.
Huh?
[RAM]
Agreed.
It's scrap.
Just an obstacle
blocking my path.
I-- I just can't help
but think it kind of looked
like it was a door, you know.
[mysterious music]
Huh?
What was that just now?
Natsuki,
did you do something?
Did I?
You were watching, right?
All I did was touch it.
I didn't do anything special,
so I don't know
what happened either.
Let's keep going.
[SUBARU]
Patrasche.
[growls]
I understand
it's scary right now
and that you're
trying to protect us,
but nothing down here's safe.
That's just the situation.
That means we
need to be prepared
to take risks at some point.
And there's no better
time than now, OK?
[growls]
She's got you whipped,
hasn't she?
Listen, if there's
got to be whipping
between me and a woman,
I'd rather be the one
who's getting whipped,
you know?
Gross.
[SUBARU]
I didn't mean it like that.
[sighs]
The second time
this has happened.
Both of 'em just disappeared
when I touched 'em.
What's the point
of walls that don't stop
anyone from going through 'em?
Uh, what's up?
Oh, well,
we haven't seen any,
so it makes sense we
didn't consider it before.
But perhaps those walls were
created to stop mabeasts.
There's also
a non-zero chance
that this could be connected
to a sandworm's tunnel.
So it would make sense
that they're for mabeasts.
[SUBARU]
Don't like that.
If you're right,
that's freaking terrifying.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Anyone else starting
to feel weirdly heavy?
[groans]
But I guess now isn't
the time to start whining.
Sure, it's a little hard
to walk, but I can keep going.
No big deal.
If we can keep up this pace,
then we might
reach our goal faster.
[RAM]
Barusu, shut up.
Uh, OK.
It just seems so boring
to not say a single thing
the whole entire time.
You think it's a fun
stroll through the park?
We all need to stay focused.
I know, but--
[ANASTASIA] Hey, now,
Natsuki, that's enough.
Read the room, will ya?
When people are already
feeling on edge,
continuing
to push their buttons
is just gonna dig you
a bigger hole, I'm afraid,
you know?
[water draining]
[pounding]
Damn it!
Why now?
What the hell?
They already let us pass
through three doors no problem.
Why get in our way after
we've come this far?
Why?
Oh, damn it.
Damn it all.
Natsuki,
that's enough.
It's not gonna
make a difference.
No matter how you look at it,
we've run into a dead end.
I know that.
Stating the obvious
doesn't help us!
[gasps]
[glass shatters]
Hey, what the hell
has your problem been
since we got down here anyway?
Nothing.
Nothing my ass.
Come on, I asked you what
your damn problem is!
I'm busting my ass here,
and you keep going [tutting].
I can hear you, you know!
So what's your freaking
problem, huh?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
just calm down, both of you.
There's no need
to get so worked up.
[SUBARU]
Shut the hell up!
Can't you see Ram
and I are trying to have
a conversation over here?
Go on.
If there's something
you've been wanting to say,
then let's hear it already.
I'm all ears, so spit it out!
You're so eager.
All you want is to keep
moving forward, correct?
Well, yeah,
damn straight, I am.
What the hell do you think we
went through all this to do?
We're gonna see the sage--
[RAM]
Wrong.
The reason we came here
was not to see the sage.
Huh?
We came here in order
to finally awaken Rem.
And I came here so I could
remember my little sister.
But look at us.
What are we even doing now?
Rem's not around.
We're wandering aimlessly.
No more games.
I'm not playing any games!
I can't help that
we ended up here.
It's not my fault.
How come when
we fell down here,
you reached out and grabbed
me and not Rem instead?
I'm sure you only thought about
what was right in front of you.
You never think
about the big picture.
Your head is full of
Ms. Emilia and Ms. Beatrice,
and that's it.
What kind of man are you?
I feel sorry for Rem.
Shut up.
[RAM] Barusu,
didn't she believe in you?
Quiet, you!
[RAM]
No, I will not.
If we're being honest,
you don't actually care
about Rem at all, do you?
Knock it off with that shit!
[growling]
Invisible Providence.
[thud]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Quit screwing with me!
This is all your
own damn fault.
Your fault,
your fault, your fault!
Do us all a favor
and die, bitch!
You disgust me.
It seriously makes
me sick to my stomach
that you look so much like Rem!
Huh?
I can't hear you!
If you still got something
you want to say, just say it.
♪ ♪
Ra.
[explosion]
Magic?
Listen, you bitch,
it's too late to come
crying and saying sorry now!
If anybody should be
saying that, it's me.
Someone like you doesn't
deserve to see Rem.
I'll slice you apart
and leave you here to rot!
Keep talking.
[ANASTASIA]
All right, that's enough.
[squelch]
There was no stopping you two.
Unfortunately, I had
to decide who'd be more useful.
I apologize.
You just-- why?
[ANASTASIA]
What?
You're the one asking me that?
I could say things
were gonna end poorly
if I let 'em be,
so I figured
I'd give you a hand.
Or could it be that you're
pissed because I stole
your prey out from under you?
And now you're coming for me?
Fine, I'll let you get away
with smooth talking me for now,
so whatever.
Hmm.
What a good choice.
Oh, you're so very clever.
I can let out a sigh
of relief, finally.
So here, how about
a little handshake
to show that we're gonna make
up and play nice from now on?
Uh.
Natsuki?
Something wrong?
No.
Not at all.
[ANASTASIA]
In that case.
[slicing noise]
[thud]
[suspenseful music]
[squelching]
[whimpers]
[screams]
[SUBARU]
Let me go!
No.
[screams]
I don't want to die!
You're already dead!
There's nothing
I can do to help you.
Damn it, why won't you just
hurry up and die already?
[suspenseful music]
[screams]
♪ ♪
[heavy breathing]
[ANASTASIA]
Don't leave me.
♪ ♪
[vomits]
It's Ram.
This is Ram's magic, I'm sure.
The bitch must have managed
to survive somehow and--
[crunching noise]
♪ ♪
Patrasche?
You were alive this whole time?
What's going on?
Is Ram dead finally?
No, it doesn't matter.
Let me ride you.
Huh?
Did you hear me?
Hey, come here!
Now, damn it.
Think you can just
disrespect me like that?
♪ ♪
Finally came
to your senses, I see.
Heh.
♪ ♪
Huh?
[clink]
[screeches]
[thud]
[squelching]
Barusu, Barusu.
If you don't wake up soon,
I'm just going
to burn off your eyelids.
[gasps]
[SUBARU]
I'm--
Barusu?
Pathetic, aren't you?
Don't bite me.
[groans]
[retching]
Thanks.
I'm OK now.
Good.
Well, I'm so glad you're
feeling better now.
Give me a break, will ya?
[ANASTASIA]
Well, thank goodness.
Finally bright eyed
and bushy tailed, are you?
[RAM]
Thankfully.
How did the surroundings look?
Not ideal.
I wasn't able to find an exit,
and none of the others
seemed close by.
Hey, Natsuki.
What's the matter?
I just wondered,
what is the miasma exactly?
Huh?
This place is technically
part of the dunes, right?
Which means there's probably
some of that miasma here, too.
To put it simply, miasma
is basically tainted mana.
And what does it do to you?
They say if you
get stuck in it,
it'll eat away
at your body and mind
until nothing's left of you.
Well, can you fight it?
Unfortunately,
our gates take in mana
automatically by nature.
So the only thing we can really
do to stop it from affecting us
is to stay as far
away as possible
from where
the miasma's thickest.
The miasma was
responsible for that.
So if we keep moving,
it'll happen again.
No.
Barusu?
Let's go.
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
Let's take the tunnel
on the left.
It's our best bet.
Ms. Anastasia, the ceiling
gets lower in this part,
so be careful.
[ANASTASIA]
OK, got it.
Thank you kindly.
[SUBARU] Ram, the footing's
kind of unstable here,
so watch your step.
[RAM]
OK, understood.
If you get cold,
don't be afraid to speak up.
I'll lend you my cloak
if you want it.
What?
Why'd you stop?
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you acting
creepy and considerate?
What exactly are you plotting?
I promise you,
I'm not plotting anything.
I just want you both
to stay safe and healthy
as possible, that's all.
You're a pervert.
That's not perverted.
How is it any different from
how Julius acts all the time?
Well, it's natural and
expected when Julius does it,
but from you,
it feels sick, kinda.
It just ain't right.
[SUBARU]
Did you just say sick?
[ANASTASIA]
The heck?
Do you smell something funny?
It smells like
something's on fire, yes.
[SUBARU]
A smell?
Here, I'll go and check it out.
If something happens,
we're leaving you as bait, OK?
So don't blame us.
[SUBARU]
You know I'm gonna curse
the hell out of if you do.
♪ ♪
[screams]
[gushing noise]
♪ ♪
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ugh!
[groans]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
[thrilling music]
♪ ♪
[screeches]
[roars]
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
Stupid.
[yells]
[explosions]
♪ ♪
[screams]
[RAM]
El Fula!
Get up.
You want to make Rem cry?
Don't you dare die.
Barusu!
[screeches]
Invisible Providence!
El Fula!
[swooshing noise]
Barusu.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
[thudding]
[screeches]
[groans]
Why did you--
I don't want Rem to cry.
[whoosh]
Come on,
don't be deadweight.
No.
[galloping noise]
Move it.
Get up,
Subaru Natsuki!
[puncturing]
Ram!
[groans]
[SHAULA]
I found you.
[theme music]
♪ ♪